https://www.work-for-rvers-and-campers.com/privacy-policy.html

Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com
Menu
RVers: Start HereWorkers On Wheels HomeAnnouncementsWOW E-mail NewsHelp Wanted Ads for RVersFeatured EmployersHome Biz Op DirectoryWork Wanted Ads from RVersThe Basics for Working RVersWorkers On Wheels Blog
RV WorkBob's RV Work ArticlesCampground WorkProperty CaretakingFlea MarketsNetwork MarketingTemp AgenciesTeaching JobsVolunteeringOnline Work
More RV WorkWriting for ProfitAgricultural JobsDisney JobsEmploymentReferral FeesRV Home BusinessSeasonal JobsTourism JobsWebsite BuildingTips for Working RVers
RV Work LifestylesDream JobsRVing w/ KidsSingle RVersSurvey PollsTestimonialsWorker's Stories
RV Work ResourcesMail ServiceResume HelpQuestions/AnswersTaxesTax and LegalBooksMags/Newsletters
WOW AdminAbout UsPrivacy PolicyDisclosureContact the EditorSite Search
Privacy Policy for Workers On Wheels -- Work-For-RVers-and-Campers.com
Privacy PolicyAt Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.This website contains links to
other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have
used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other
website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and
privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These
sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise
caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question
before continuing to use it.
Social MediaYou may notice links on this website
to social media sites. When you click on them or leave a
comment, your browser connects directly with that site and sends
information such as your IP address, the date and time of your visit,
and information about how you use the social site. Below are links to
the privacy policies of each platform.RedditTumblerPinterest.comGoogle and YouTubeTwitterFacebookAbout Our CookiesA cookie is a string of information that Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.Advertising Cookies We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. We share this information with these companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.You may opt out of personalized ads for over 125 different ad networks. Click here to do that.Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the Google ad opt-out page. This link from Google provides more information about how Google manages data in its ad products.Affiliate Products and ServicesWe receive an affiliate commission for some of the products and services sold on Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com.The affiliate services platforms we use are Amazon, ClickBank, and Commission Junction.By clicking on a product or service link, you consent to that platform's use of cookies, as outlined in the link below.Amazon privacy policy.ClickBank privacy policy.Commission Junction privacy policy.Coleen Sykora is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com, amazonsupply.com, or myhabit.com.Refusing CookiesYou can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.Personally Identifiable InformationWorkers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:•    To run and operate our site.•    To display content on the site correctly.•    To improve customer service.•    To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.•    To personalize your user experience.•    To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.•    To improve our site.•    To improve our products and services.•    To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.•    To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.•    To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.•    To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.•    To process your order for products or services.Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.Specifically, if you subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for your first name and will require your email address.If you complete a form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for information relevant to the purpose of the form.If you submit content to us, we will ask for your name and email address. Photos you include with your submission, or details in your submission, may personally identify you.If you request to be notified about comments on any content you submit to us, or request to be notified when others submit content, we will require your first name and your email address.If you purchase a product or service from us, we will collect your name, email address, telephone number, billing address, shipping address, and your payment information including credit or debit card number, expiration date, and security code numbers.We use PayPal to process payments, including
payments you make with a debit or credit card. PayPal's privacy policy.Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name, telephone number, and any other information you voluntarily provide to us.This information may be collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, sign up to join our email list, request some other service from us, make a website or email submission or otherwise submit information to us, or make a purchase from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, respond to visitor inquiries, and provide the information, products, and services you request.When you place an order for products or services through us, you must include adequate personal information to complete payment and allow for delivery of the purchase. If the product or service you order is delivered by a third party, when you place your order, you are authorizing us to provide your personal information to them.When you send us a story, article, tip, profile, menu, recipe, review, news release, resume, ad, suggestion, question, comment, testimonial, or other submission, we ask you to provide contact information to prevent unauthorized postings and publication. We may publish your name, email address, phone number, mailing address, website address, and other information you voluntarily include in your submission. When you make a submission to this website, you are authorizing us to provide your personal and business contact information to our website readers and to post it publicly on the world wide web.Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored. You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud.
We offer RSS to make it
easy to follow our content updates. View their privacy policies at Feedly, MyYahoo, MyMSN. Non-personally Identifiable InformationWe may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)Workers On Wheels work-for-rvers-and-campers.com has not sold any personal information in the past 12 months, nor at any prior time.Children's Privacy ProtectionThis website is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental consent to use this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.Release of InformationIf we sell Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.Data StoragePersonally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.If you wish to review your information stored on the SiteSell servers for Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com, click on this link. You can also edit, download, or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on that link.Some information is collected by third-party services. These include AWeber, GoDaddy, PayPal, and Facebook.
How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe
provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to
protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted
personally identifiable information through our website and would like
to update that information or have it deleted from our records, click on
this link. Updates and Effective DateWorkers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.If you do not agree to Workers On Wheels -- Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, do not use this site or any services offered by this site.Your explicit consent, or use of this site, indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.An exception to this privacy policy would be if we were required to do so by law.Last updated: January 1, 2020Go to the Work For RVers And Campers home page.
Go to our blog to see what's new here on Workers On Wheels - Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com and to find more info about earning a living while full-time RVing.Disclosure: We receive compensation from advertisers, affiliate
relationships, and site sponsors
Jen Work Camping
Most Recently
Moab KOA Holiday Campground Moab, Utah Dec 10, 20 09:10 PM 	Magnificent Views Of The Red Rocks
Make us your headquarters as you explore the adventure Capital of the West. We are located 15 minutes from Arches Read More
You can produce an income
Work Camping.
Coleen and Bob Workers On Wheels Founders
Post Your Help Wanted Ad on Workers On Wheels - Click Here***
Copyright 1992-2020 All Rights Reserved - No
reproduction permitted without written permission.
Contact Info -- Jim Erickson, Workers On Wheels,
Work-for-RVers-and-Campers.com
Disclosure: This site provides helpful and
entertaining information thanks to compensation received from quality
advertisers and affiliate relationships.Privacy Policy
Workers On Wheels is our website and newsletter about working while RVing -- working
while living in a home on wheels. There are so many kinds of work to do while
RVing and camping (what some campers call workcamping or work camping). We help
RV workers -- whether snowbirds or full-time RVers -- find campground
jobs, volunteer jobs,  jobs with RV spaces, seasonal jobs, mobile employment, short-term paid employment, and
other ways to earn an income and cut expenses while enjoying life in a recreational vehicle. Thanks for visiting our WOW website! ~ Jim, your Workers On Wheels editor, at work-for-RVers-and-campers.com
